<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Trusted Cybersecurity</title>
    <link>https://maxibelino.github.io/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Trusted Cybersecurity</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Maximiliano Belino</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 15:23:13 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://maxibelino.github.io/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PHP up to 7.3 Vulnerability. LFI to RCE</title>
      <link>https://maxibelino.github.io/en/posts/phplfitorce/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 15:23:13 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://maxibelino.github.io/en/posts/phplfitorce/</guid>
      <description>This post is only in spanish.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybersecurity Services</title>
      <link>https://maxibelino.github.io/en/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:07:23 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://maxibelino.github.io/en/services/</guid>
      <description>Red Team Services A proactive approach to testing your organization&amp;rsquo;s resilience against advanced attacks. Our team simulates real-world threat scenarios to identify critical vulnerabilities and strengthen your systems&amp;rsquo; defenses.&#xA;Open Source Intelligence (OSINT) Harness the power of publicly available information. Our OSINT service collects, analyzes, and transforms online data into actionable intelligence to anticipate threats and protect your interests.&#xA;Network Security Audits Ensure the integrity of your network infrastructures with a comprehensive audit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://maxibelino.github.io/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 12:40:35 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://maxibelino.github.io/en/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi there! I’m Maximiliano, a cybersecurity enthusiast driven by the exciting challenges this field brings every day. I hold a degree in Telecommunications Engineering from the University of the Republic (UDELAR) in Uruguay, along with a Master’s in Offensive Security from Campusciberseguridad (Spain), endorsed by the Catholic University of Murcia (UCAM).&#xA;Since February 2023, I’ve been an OSCP (OffSec) certified professional, a milestone that showcases my commitment to continuous learning and tackling complex security problems.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
